Huh?
The End
Big brother, would you like to have a party with me?
Would you like to have a party with me?
Um...
What was that?
You're looking for someone, right?
A friend of the party!
That's true, but...
Then please join the party with me!
My name is...
Naruseina!
As you can see, I'm a martial artist!
I'm Raust.
I'm a Chiushi.
Just in case.
W-W-W-Wait a minute!
Who are you?
I'm Amast, a member of the Adventurer Guild Martat Branch.
And I don't care about that!
Do you know who that man is?
Who... is he?
He's a useless Raust.
What?
That's right.
Chiushi's only use is the Heel of the First-class Magic.
He's been a adventurer since he was a child,
and he's been using it for a long time.
He's still useless,
and he's useless.
I remember that day,
he was invited to a party called the Heel of the First-class Magic,
but he was kicked out because he couldn't use the Heel of the First-class Magic.
Everyone in town knows that he's useless,
so no one invites him to the party.
He's in trouble with money,
and if he goes to a party with that guy,
he won't be able to stay in the Rokuna Yard.
Oh, I have the money, so I'm fine.
Hey!
Wait!
I'm sorry to say this,
but there are a lot of adventurers in town who are bad-tempered.
Don't show off your money like that.
Really?
Thank you for your kindness!
You've just become an adventurer.
What? You know that?
Well, all the equipment is brand new.
Oh, right.
I'll introduce you to a good party for beginners.
You'll get a good amount of money if you're a good adventurer.
Oh, that's fine.
I've been deciding to have a party with that guy for a long time.
Bye!
Wait!
Oh, my.
I don't know what's going on.
I saw it!
Wait, what?
It's been like this for a long time?
You have to be an older brother.
Here you go.
What is this?
It's a party's final delivery.
If you don't submit this to the guild,
you can't even get rid of the quest,
and you can't even get rid of the quest when you're in trouble.
Oh.
I finally met you.
Then, can you write your name here?
What?
It's your name. You can write your name, right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Here you go.
Here's your money.
Oh, I see.
It's a good deal!
Now we're officially partying together.
Nice to meet you, brother.
Nice to meet you, too.
The M.A.A.T. is still in the dark.
We don't know what kind of monsters the M.A.A.T. owners are.
The reason why there are so many unknown parts is because there is room for adventure.
So, naturally, the adventurers gather.
The M.A.A.T. has grown into the largest
and the most powerful monster in the world.
But there are some places where monsters appear
because of the magic power that comes out of the labyrinth.
The eastern mountainous area,
the northern forest,
and the southern desert.
Among them, the West Forest is a place for beginners,
where there are only relatively weak monsters.
There are many large monsters, so you can't really meet them.
At that point, if it's a labyrinth, there are monsters that can beat you.
And if you don't go deep, there are no strong monsters,
so I thought there would be no problem.
I see.
Well, if it's possible...
Did you say something?
No, it's nothing.
This is the entrance to the labyrinth.
Then let's go.
Oh, wait a minute!
I'll walk in front of you!
What?
I'm a martial artist, and you're a swordsman.
I'm the one who's going to lead you!
Well, usually, I am, but...
Come on, let's go!
She's fine, but...
I wonder if she can fight properly.
How is it, big brother?
I'm amazing, right?
Yeah, I was surprised.
He-he!
This is the magic stone.
Adventurers usually make a mold by selling this to guilds.
What do guilds do with the magic stone they bought?
Magic stones have magic power, so they have many ways to use it.
And if you're going to do this much of an adventure,
it's a natural knowledge to know.
I'm not good at the science.
How much is this?
Goblins aren't very expensive.
You can't get a magic stone that sells at a high price unless you defeat a strong monster.
That's true.
Well, this is about the price of today's residence, but...
How about we go a little deeper?
Yes!
I'll protect you if I have to!
Don't worry!
That's very kind of you.
Naruseena!
What's wrong?
Oh!
Onii-san, how did you know?
The color of the floor was a little different from the others.
I didn't notice at all.
But finding traps is usually a job of a thief, right?
Onii-san, you're a healer.
I've been doing adventures for a long time, so I've been able to do a lot of things.
Oh, is that so?
Why is Ork in such a place?
Is something wrong?
Ork is a monster called the Demon of the Middle
And the strength and strength of the
It's a powerful opponent that's also suitable for the monsters of the virtual world.
Normally, it shouldn't be up here.
Should we run away?
No, I don't think we can beat it if we work together.
Of course, I won't say it's impossible.
If Onii-san says he can do it, I won't object!
All right, it's decided.
It's like he kicked a rock.
But it's slow.
Naruseyama!
Damn it!
I'm going to kill you!
Are you hurt?
Yes.
Onii-san, are you really a healer?
I've been doing adventures for a long time, so I can do a little melee fighting.
It wasn't much of a thing.
Naruseyama, your arm...
Oh, it's a scratch.
It'll be blocked soon.
No, let's treat it properly.
But...
Come on, show me.
Heal.
It's a lot different from Goblin's.
It has a lot of magic power, and it sells at a high price.
Well, what should we do?
We've shown you your power, and we've earned enough.
You can go home now.
I'm still here!
Let's hunt some more monsters.
Yes!
The next day
You guys are hunting monsters in half a day?
Hey, Raust!
You took Naruseyama to the maze, didn't you?
And this is a lot of magic stones.
Did you suddenly go to the Middle-East?
No, it's not.
He was wandering around the upper layer.
It's true.
I said I wanted to go lower, but he said no.
I see.
He believes you.
Yes.
Actually, there have been some reports of such spirits lately.
What?
Our client's movements are also in a hurry.
I think something is happening in the maze.
What is something?
You don't know anything about a person like me, do you?
So, you're going to buy all these magic stones, right?
Yes, I'll take care of that.
Yes, maido ali!
I'll get the money ready, so wait a minute.
Amost, you look very happy.
The guild staff buy the magic stones from the adventurers in charge.
The reward is added according to the amount.
So, the more we get the magic stones, the more...
My heart will be shaking.
That's why.
Do your best for me, too, Naru-Seina.
What? So much?
That's right.
I'll give half of it to you.
Of course.
But, even if I give half of it, the 10 times the amount I've received so far...
The 10 times...
What's wrong?
Inazuma's sword didn't give me a fair share.
It seems that it was also quite a trick.
That's terrible!
That's right, Amost.
When the guild is in trouble, you help them, right?
Of course.
If I pay the fixed amount, I'll be in a big trouble.
What should I do?
No, it's okay.
But...
I've already set up a new party.
I'll forget about the previous party.
Thank you very much.
Nishiro Yato, Nishiro Yato...
Amost.
H-Hansam, what's wrong?
It seems that Raust was just here.
I don't think he's been to a new party.
I don't think anyone would want to be partying in a place where they've been to such a place.
It's just that...
There's a girl who's a bit of a pain.
Naruseina.
I don't think she's a girl with blue hair.
Yes, that's right.
She's beautiful and blue.
I see.
What?
Oh, Raust-san, welcome!
Is that the new party member?
What? You already know her?
It's been rumored that the incompetent Raust is going to have a party.
So, are you going to have dinner today?
I want to have dinner, but first I want to secure a room.
Then, talk to your mother in the back.
Room? Are you two going to share a room?
A room? A room with you?
Don't tease me, Mary-san.
It's decided by the two of you, right?
Oh, really?
Since the second floor is open, you can choose whichever room you like.
But before that, you must be hungry.
Thank you.
It's fine if we share a room.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Oh...
Thank you.
No, this is all I can do.
I've decided!
When I grow up, I'll be an adventurer!
I'll be an adventurer and have a party with you!
Don't worry, Raust-san.
I'll protect you!
Since that day, I've been training my body to become an adventurer.
For the sake of today.
So, I heard that my brother was kicked out of the party, and I came to this town.
I had a party with my brother, and I defeated the Goblins.
It was all for my brother.
Even I didn't notice it.
Since then, I've grown taller, and the clothes I wear are completely different.
Above all, the color of my hair is different.
It's natural that you don't know.
My brother has always been strong.
He doesn't need my help.
What are you talking about, Naruseyna?
You're protecting your brother, right?
What are you going to do when you're weak?
It's decided by yourself, so do it until the end.
I'm going to go.
But why are the people of this town...
They call such a great brother, Munoz.
I don't know what to do.
I just want to protect you.
I can only understand the heartbeat of your heart.
I can't live alone.
I'm a living treasure.
I'm not alone.
I'm on a road of thorns.
And we're going.
I wish I could get a breeze.
Even if the blowing wind isn't there.
But if I become stronger.
If I can light up that life.
If I don't give up, there won't be an end.
It continues far away.
I believe in the only way.